Irving Berlin Collection
Music Division, Library of Congress
- Non-Show Music (Box-folder 29-31, 220-250, Mapcase 3)
  - How much I love you, Written for Reaching for the moon; Verse later used for How deep is the ocean?
    - Typescript lyric sheets; [12] leaves (Box-folder 230/40)
  - How was I to know
    - Manuscript lead sheet; [1] p. (Box-folder 230/41)
    - Typescript lyric sheet; [1] leaf (Box-folder 230/41)
  - How's your heart?
    - Typescript lyric sheets; [3] leaves (Box-folder 230/42)
  - Hurry back to my bamboo shack
    - Fair copy (Kresa) manuscript piano-vocal score; 4 p. (Box-folder 230/43)
  - Hustle along
    - Manuscript lead sheet; [1] p. (Box-folder 230/44)
  - I am leaving tonight on the Midnight Express
    - Manuscript lyric sheet; [1] p., In shorthand (Box-folder 231/1)
    - Typescript translation of shorthand; [1] p., With annotations (Box-folder 231/1)
  - I beg your pardon, dear old Broadway
    - Fair copy (Kresa) manuscript piano-vocal score; 5 p. (Box-folder 231/2)
  - I can die with a smile on my face
    - Manuscript lead sheet; [1] p., On verso: unknown sketch (Box-folder 231/3)
  - I can't do it by myself, 1986 version of You can't do it by yourself
    - Typescript lyric sheets; [2] leaves (Box-folder 231/4)
  - I can't do without you, Alternate title: Without you
    - Manuscript piano-vocal score; [3] p., No lyrics (Box-folder 231/5)
  - I can't remember
    - Manuscript piano-vocal score; [3] p., No lyrics (Box-folder 231/6)
    - Manuscript piano score; [2] p. (Box-folder 231/6)
    - Sketch; [1] p. (Box-folder 231/6)
    - Fair copy (Kresa) manuscript piano-vocal score; 4 p. (Box-folder 231/6)
    - Typescript lyric sheet; [1] leaf (Box-folder 231/6)
    - Sheet music (Box-folder 231/6)
  - I could be a sweet heart to you
    - Sketch; [1] p. (Box-folder 231/7)
  - I could live on love and kisses
    - Manuscript lead sheet; [1] p. (Box-folder 231/8)
    - Typescript lyric sheets; [4] leaves (Box-folder 231/8)
  - I couldn't speak any English
    - Holograph lyric sheet; [1] leaf (Box-folder 231/9)
  - I don't think we'd better send them back
    - Typescript lyric sheets; [6] leaves (Box-folder 231/10)
  - I don't want to be married see also Face the music
    - Typescript lyric sheet; [1] leaf (Box-folder 231/11)
  - I felt that something was going to happen, Alternate title: Something was going to happen
    - Holograph lyric sheet; [1] leaf (Box-folder 231/12)
  - I have everything
    - Sketch; [1] p. (Box-folder 231/13)
  - I have just one heart for just one boy, Alternate title: I have just one heart; Introduced in The canary
    - Fair copy (Kresa) manuscript piano-vocal score; 4 p. (Box-folder 231/14)
  - I haven't got a home to go to
    - Typescript lyric sheets; [2] leaves (Box-folder 231/15)
  - I just wanna know my baby loves me
    - Manuscript lead sheet; [1] p. (Box-folder 231/16)
  - I keep running away from you, Later revised to become Glad to be home from Mr. President
    - Copyist's manuscript piano-vocal score; 2 p. (Box-folder 231/17)
    - Manuscript lead sheet; [1] p., May, 1955 (Box-folder 231/17)
    - Manuscript lead sheet; [2] p., April, 1957 (Box-folder 231/17)
    - Printed manuscript lead sheets; 2 p. each, 2 copies (Box-folder 231/17)
    - Typescript lyric sheets; [9] leaves (Box-folder 231/17)
  - I know that lady
    - Holograph lyric sheet; [1] leaf (Box-folder 231/18)
  - I like Ike
    - Manuscript full score; 21 p. (Box-folder 31/1)
    - Manuscript lead sheet; [3] p. (Box-folder 31/1)
    - Manuscript parts (Box-folder 31/1)
    - Sheet music, Piano/4 part vocal (Box-folder 31/1)
  - I love a small town
    - Typescript lyric sheet; [1] leaf, With annotations; Manuscript on verso: 427 St. Ann's Ave., George Robinson (Box-folder 231/19)
  - I love my neighbor
    - Sketches(3); [5] p. (Box-folder 231/20)
    - Manuscript lyric sheet; [1] leaf (Box-folder 231/20)
    - Typescript lyric sheet; [2] leaves (Box-folder 231/20)
  - I love to quarrel with you
    - Fair copy (Kresa) manuscript piano-vocal score; 3 p. (Box-folder 231/21)
    - Typescript lyric sheet; [1] leaf (Box-folder 231/21)
  - I love to stay at home
    - Manuscript piano-vocal score; [4] p. (Box-folder 231/22)
    - Fair copy (Kresa) manuscript piano-vocal score; 4 p. (Box-folder 231/22)
  - I love you more each day, Music by Ted Snyder
    - Fair copy (Kresa) manuscript piano-vocal score; 5 p. (Box-folder 231/23)
  - I love you - you love him see also Easter parade
    - Copyist's manuscript piano-vocal score; 3 p., Transparencies (Box-folder 231/24)
    - Manuscript piano-vocal score; [1] p. (Box-folder 231/24)
    - Manuscript lead sheet; [1] p. (Box-folder 231/24)
    - Photocopies of manuscript piano-vocal score; 3 p. each, 2 copies (Box-folder 231/24)
    - Holograph lyric sheet; [1] leaf (Box-folder 231/24)
    - Typescript lyric sheet; [1] leaf, With annotations (Box-folder 231/24)
    - Typescript lyric sheets; [11] leaves (Box-folder 231/24)
  - I might go home tonight, Vincent Bryan/Irving Berlin
    - Typescript lyric sheet; [1] leaf (Box-folder 231/25)
  - I never had a chance, Introduced on Gulf Oil's Good gulf program by Frank Parker
    - Manuscript lead sheet; [1] p., Feb., 1933 (Box-folder 231/26)
    - Manuscript lead sheet; [1] p., Mar., 1934 (Box-folder 231/26)
    - Sketch; [1] p. (Box-folder 231/26)
    - Typescript lyric sheets; [5] leaves (Box-folder 231/26)
  - I paid my income tax today
    - Manuscript piano-vocal score; [3] p. (Box-folder 231/27)
    - Manuscript piano score; [1] p. (Box-folder 231/27)
    - Sketches; [7] p. (Box-folder 231/27)
    - Typescript lyric sheets; [9] leaves (Box-folder 231/27)
    - Sheet music, 2 copies; Without cover (Box-folder 231/27)
  - I still like Ike
    - Manuscript full score; 10 p. (Box-folder 31/2)
    - Manuscript piano-conductor score and parts (Box-folder 31/2)
    - Manuscript vocal score; [2] p., Arranged for male voices (Box-folder 31/2)
    - Printed manuscript vocal sheets; [1] p. each, 2 copies; Arranged for male voices (Box-folder 31/2)
    - Manuscript piano-vocal score; 9 p. (Box-folder 232/1)
    - Copyist's manuscript piano-vocal score; [1] 8 p., Transparencies (Box-folder 232/1)
    - Copyist's manuscript lead sheet; [1] p., Transparency; Arranged for male voices (Box-folder 232/1)
    - Sketches(2); [2] p. (Box-folder 232/1)
    - Printed piano-vocal scores; 8 p. each, 2 copies; With annotations (Box-folder 232/1)
    - Printed piano-vocal scores; 8 p. each, 2 copies (Box-folder 232/1)
    - Holograph lyric sheets; [5] leaves (Box-folder 232/1)
    - Typescript lyric sheets; [16] leaves (Box-folder 232/1)
    - Printed piano-vocal score; 17 p., Collection of 'Ike' songs by Irving Berlin (Box-folder 232/1)
  - I threw a kiss in the ocean, Alternate title: I spoke to the ocean
    - Manuscript piano-vocal score; [4] p. (Box-folder 232/2)
    - Manuscript lead sheet with piano score; [2] p., Verse only (Box-folder 232/2)
    - Manuscript piano score; [3] p. (Box-folder 232/2)
    - Printed manuscript piano-vocal scores; [4] p. each, 2 copies (Box-folder 232/2)
    - Typescript lyric sheets; [10] leaves (Box-folder 232/2)
    - Sheet music, 2 copies; Without cover (Box-folder 232/2)
    - Sheet music (Box-folder 232/2)
  - I wanna dance with the girl in my arms, Written for Say it with music
    - Typescript lyric sheets; [5] leaves (Box-folder 232/3)
  - I want a harem of my own
    - Manuscript lead sheet; [1] p., With annotations (Box-folder 232/4)
    - Typescript lyric sheet; [1] leaf (Box-folder 232/4)
  - I want to go back to Michigan (down on the farm), I want to go back to Michigan down on the farm
    - Manuscript lead sheet; [2] p., Laid in: sketch; [2] p. (Box-folder 232/5)
    - Fair copy (Kresa) manuscript piano-vocal score; 4 p. (Box-folder 232/5)
    - Typescript lyric sheets; [3] leaves (Box-folder 232/5)
  - I want to go back to the farm
    - Manuscript lead sheet; [1] p., At top: Belle Baker (Box-folder 232/6)
    - Holograph lyric sheets; [3] leaves, On verso of one leaf: holograph lyrics for "Someday you'll come back to me" (Box-folder 232/6)
    - Typescript lyric sheets; [2] leaves (Box-folder 232/6)
  - I want to jazz my troubles away, Alternate title: I want to dance my troubles away
    - Typescript lyric sheets; [7] leaves (Box-folder 232/7)
  - I want to marry you
    - Photocopy of typescript lyric sheet; [1] leaf, Original from I'll make you love me lyric sheet (Box-folder 232/8)
  - I want you to meet my girl, Written for Blue skies, but not used
    - Typescript lyric sheet; [1] leaf (Box-folder 232/9)
  - I wasn't doing anything wrong
    - Typescript lyric sheets; [2] leaves (Box-folder 232/10)
  - I went to a doctor
    - Typescript lyric sheet; [1] leaf, With annotations (Box-folder 232/11)
  - I wish that you was my gal, Molly, Music by Ted Snyder
    - Manuscript piano-vocal score; [4] p. (Box-folder 232/12)
  - I'd rather see a minstrel show
    - Photocopy of sheet music, Without cover (Box-folder 232/13)
  - I'd rather not dance again, Written for Blue skies, but not used
    - Manuscript piano-vocal score; [3] p., No lyric (Box-folder 232/14)
    - Typescript lyric sheet; [1] leaf, With annotations (Box-folder 232/14)
    - Typescript lyric sheets; [4] leaves (Box-folder 232/14)
  - If all the girls I knew were like you
    - Fair copy (Kresa) manuscript piano-vocal score; 4 p. (Box-folder 232/15)
  - If I had my way (I'd be a farmer)
    - Typescript lyric sheets; [2] leaves (Box-folder 232/16)
  - If I had my way, I'd live among the gypsies
    - Manuscript piano-vocal score; 3 p. (Box-folder 232/17)
    - Typescript lyric sheet; [1] leaf (Box-folder 232/17)
    - Typescript history of the song; [3] leaves (Box-folder 232/17)
  - If I had you
    - Manuscript piano-vocal score; [4] p. (Box-folder 232/18)
    - Fair copy (Kresa) manuscript piano-vocal score; 4 p. (Box-folder 232/18)
  - If I thought you wouldn't tell, Music by Ted Snyder
    - Fair copy (Kresa) manuscript piano-vocal score; 4 p. (Box-folder 232/19)
  - If it wasn't for my wife and baby
    - Typescript lyric sheet; [1] leaf (Box-folder 232/20)
  - If only you belonged to me (and I belonged to you)
    - Manuscript piano score; [2] p. (Box-folder 232/21)
    - Manuscript lead sheet; [1] p. (Box-folder 232/21)
    - Sketch; [2] p. (Box-folder 232/21)
  - If that’s your idea of a wonderful time (take me home), Alternate title: If that's your idea of a wonderful time-take me home
    - Manuscript piano-vocal score; [3] p. (Box-folder 232/22)
    - Fair copy (Kresa) manuscript piano-vocal score; 5 p. (Box-folder 232/22)
  - If the managers only thought the same as mother, Music by Ted Snyder
    - Fair copy (Kresa) manuscript piano-vocal score; 5 p. (Box-folder 232/23)
  - If they were all like you see also Watch your step
    - Sketch; [2] p. (Box-folder 232/24)
  - If you believe
    - Manuscript score; 24 p. (Box-folder 232/25)
    - Manuscript parts (Box-folder 232/25)
  - If you didn’t know how old you were, Alternate title: Old men
    - Typescript lyric sheets; [7] leaves (Box-folder 232/26)
  - If you don't like my apples
    - Typescript lyric sheet; [1] leaf, With annotations (Box-folder 232/27)
    - Typescript lyric sheets; [2] leaves (Box-folder 232/27)
  - If you don’t want me (why do you hang around?), Alternate title: If you don't want me
    - Fair copy (Kresa) manuscript piano-vocal score; 3 p. (Box-folder 232/28)
  - If you don’t want my peaches (you’d better stop shaking my tree)
    - Manuscript piano-vocal score; [4] p. (Box-folder 232/29)
    - Fair copy (Kresa) manuscript piano-vocal score; 2 p. (Box-folder 232/29)
  - If you haven't got an ear for music see also I've got an ear for music, Written for Mr. President, but not used
    - Manuscript piano-vocal score; [3] p. (Box-folder 232/30)
    - Printed piano-vocal scores; 3 p. each, 2 copies (Box-folder 232/30)
    - Typescript lyric sheets; [2] leaves (Box-folder 232/30)
  - If you know how to strut
    - Manuscript piano score; [3] p. (Box-folder 232/31)
  - Ike for four more years
    - Manuscript piano-conductor score with parts; [3] p., Key of C major; On title page of score: general utility (Box-folder 232/32)
    - Manuscript piano-conductor score with parts; [3] p., Key of E-flat major; On title page of score: Mr. Berlin's arr. (Box-folder 232/33)
    - Manuscript score; [8] p., Key of E-flat major; Arranged by Glover; On title page of score: solo arr. (Box-folder 232/34)
    - Manuscript score; [8] p., Key of C major; Arranged by Glover (Box-folder 232/34)
    - Copyist's manuscript piano-vocal score; [1] p. each, 2 copies, transparencies (Box-folder 232/34)
    - Manuscript piano-vocal score; [2] p. (Box-folder 232/34)
    - Printed manuscript piano-vocal score; [1] p. each, 2 copies (Box-folder 232/34)
    - Printed piano-vocal score; [1] p. (Box-folder 232/34)
    - Typescript lyric sheets; [4] leaves (Box-folder 232/34)
    - Manuscript piano score and parts; [14] p., Transparencies; Titles have been cut away from top of all pages (Box-folder 232/34)
    - Copyist's manuscript vocal part; [1] p., Transparency; At top left: Mixed voices (Box-folder 232/34)
    - Copyist's manuscript vocal part; [1] p., Transparency; At top left: Male voices (T.T.B.B.) (Box-folder 232/34)
  - Ike, Ike (the Yiddish ball player) see also Jake! Jake! The Yiddish ball player
    - Manuscript lead sheet; [1] p. (Box-folder 233/1)
    - Sketch; [1] p., Title on verso: Ike & Ike (Box-folder 233/1)
    - Typescript lyric sheets; [3] leaves (Box-folder 233/1)
  - I'll hang on to you like last winter's hat
    - Sketch; [1] p. (Box-folder 233/2)
  - I'll know better the next time see also Miss Liberty, Alternate titles: The next time I fall in love; Next time
    - Copyist's manuscript, photocopy and negative photocopy of piano-vocal score; 5 p. each, No lyric (Box-folder 233/3)
    - Copyist's manuscript piano-vocal score; [4] p., No lyric (Box-folder 233/3)
    - Sketch; [1] p. (Box-folder 233/3)
    - Fair copy (Kresa) manuscript piano-vocal score; [3] p. (Box-folder 233/3)
    - Holograph lyric sheet; [1] leaf (Box-folder 233/3)
    - Typescript lyric sheets, With annotations (Box-folder 233/3)
      - 1957; [5] leaves
      - 1982; [4] leaves
      - 1985; [4] leaves
  - I'll make it warm for you
    - Typescript lyric sheet; [1] leaf, At bottom: Original (Box-folder 233/4)
  - I'll make you love me
    - Sketch; [1] p. (Box-folder 233/5)
    - Holograph lyric sheet; [1] leaf (Box-folder 233/5)
    - Typescript lyric sheet; [1] leaf (Box-folder 233/5)
  - I'll miss you in the evening see also Venetian Isles
    - Manuscript piano-vocal score; [3] p. (Box-folder 233/6)
  - I'll still remember you
    - Typescript lyric sheet; [1] leaf (Box-folder 233/7)
  - I'll take you back to Italy, Alternate title: Sunny Italy; Introduced in Jack o'lantern
    - Fair copy (Kresa) manuscript piano-vocal score; 4 p. (Box-folder 233/8)
  - I'm a happy married man, Music by Ted Snyder
    - Manuscript piano-vocal score; [3] p. (Box-folder 233/9)
    - Fair copy (Kresa) manuscript piano-vocal score; 3 p. (Box-folder 233/9)
  - I'm a Quaker's daughter from the Latin Quarter see also Music box revue, 1938-1939
    - Typescript lyric sheet; [1] leaf (Box-folder 233/10)
  - I'm afraid, pretty maid, I'm afraid
    - Manuscript piano-vocal score; [4] p. (Box-folder 233/11)
    - Fair copy (Kresa) manuscript piano-vocal score; 5 p. (Box-folder 233/11)
  - I'm beginning to miss you
    - Manuscript piano-vocal score; 2 p., Transparencies (Box-folder 233/12)
    - Manuscript lead sheet; [1] p. each, 2 copies (Box-folder 233/12)
    - Typescript lyric sheets; [2] leaves (Box-folder 233/12)
  - I'm crazy 'bout you
    - Sketch; [1] p. (Box-folder 233/13)
  - I'm down in Honolulu looking them over
    - Sketch; [1] p., On verso: unidentified sketch (Box-folder 233/14)
    - Fair copy (Kresa) manuscript piano-vocal score; 3 p. (Box-folder 233/14)
  - I'm getting old in New Guinea
    - Typescript lyric sheet; [1] leaf (Box-folder 233/15)
  - I'm getting strong for you, Written for Watch your step, but not used
    - Holograph lyric sheets; [2] leaves (Box-folder 233/16)
    - Typescript lyric sheet; [1] leaf, With holograph annotations (Box-folder 233/16)
  - I'm going back to the farm
    - Fair copies (Kresa) manuscript piano-vocal score; 5 p. each, 2 copies (Box-folder 233/17)
  - I'm going on a long vacation, Music by Ted Snyder
    - Manuscript piano-vocal score; [3] p. (Box-folder 233/18)
    - Fair copy (Kresa) manuscript piano-vocal score; 3 p. (Box-folder 233/18)
  - I'm going to hang around, Alternate title: I'll hang around
    - Typescript lyric sheet; [1] leaf (Box-folder 233/19)
  - I'm gonna pin my medal on the girl I left behind, Introduced in Ziegfeld follies of 1918; Alternate title: I'll pin my medal on the girl I left behind
    - Fair copy (Kresa) manuscript piano-vocal score; 4 p. (Box-folder 233/20)
    - Typescript lyric sheets; [2] leaves (Box-folder 233/20)
  - I'm happy
    - Manuscript parts (Box-folder 233/21)
  - I'm looking for a daddy longlegs, Alternate title: Daddy long legs
    - Fair copy (Kresa) manuscript piano-vocal score; 4 p. (Box-folder 233/22)
  - I'm not afraid
    - Copyist's manuscript piano-vocal score; 3 p., Transparencies (Box-folder 233/23)
    - Manuscript piano-vocal score; [3] p. (Box-folder 233/23)
    - Manuscript lead sheet; [2] p., No lyrics (Box-folder 233/23)
    - Manuscript lead sheet; [1] p., With lyrics (Box-folder 233/23)
    - Sketch; [1] p. (Box-folder 233/23)
    - Printed manuscript piano-vocal scores; 3 p. each, 2 copies (Box-folder 233/23)
    - Holograph lyrics on envelope; [1] leaf (Box-folder 233/23)
    - Typescript lyric sheets; [3] leaves (Box-folder 233/23)
    - Sheet music, 2 copies; Without cover (Box-folder 233/23)
  - I'm not prepared
    - Fair copy (Kresa) manuscript piano-vocal score; [4] p. (Box-folder 233/24)
  - I'm playing fire
    - Fair copy (Kresa) manuscript piano-vocal score; 4 p. (Box-folder 233/25)
    - Typescript lyric sheets; [9] leaves (Box-folder 233/25)
  - I'm Spanish
    - Manuscript score; 18 p. (Box-folder 233/26)
  - I gave her my heart in Acapulco, Alternate title: In Acapulco
    - Manuscript lead sheet; [1] p. (Box-folder 233/27)
    - Manuscript piano score; [2] p. (Box-folder 233/27)
    - Printed manuscript piano-vocal scores; 3 p. each, 2 copies (Box-folder 233/27)
    - Holograph lyric sheet; [1] leaf, Found in In old San Juan folder on back of typescript lyric sheet (Box-folder 233/27)
    - Typescript lyric sheet; [6] leaves (Box-folder 233/27)
    - Sheet music, 2 copies; Without cover, with annotations (Box-folder 233/27)
    - Sheet music, 2 copies; Without cover (Box-folder 233/27)
    - Orchestra parts, Arranged for orchestra, key of A-flat major (Box-folder 233/28)
    - Orchestra parts, Arranged for orchestra, key of B-flat major (Box-folder 233/29)
    - Orchestra parts, Arranged for orchestra, key of F major (Box-folder 233/30)
  - In Napoli
    - Typescript lyric sheet; [1] leaf (Box-folder 234/1)
  - In old San Juan
    - Sketches; [3] p. (Box-folder 234/2)
    - Typescript lyric sheet; [1] leaf, With annotations (Box-folder 234/2)
    - Typescript lyric sheets; [5] leaves (Box-folder 234/2)
  - In the morning, Introduced in Mammy
    - Manuscript lead sheet; [1] p. (Box-folder 234/3)
  - In the twilight
    - Photocopy of holograph lyric sheet; [1] leaf (Box-folder 234/4)
  - Innocent Bessie Brown
    - Manuscript piano-vocal score; [4] p. (Box-folder 234/5)
  - Inspiration
    - Sketches; [2] p. (Box-folder 234/6)
  - Is everybody satisfied?
    - Holograph lyric sheet; [1] leaf (Box-folder 234/7)
  - Is that nice? see also (I ask you) Is that nice? from Reaching for the moon
    - Manuscript lead sheets; [1] p. each, 2 copies; No lyrics (Box-folder 234/8)
    - Sketch; [2] p. (Box-folder 234/8)
  - Israel
    - Copyist's manuscript piano-vocal score; 2 p., Transparencies (Box-folder 234/9)
    - Sketch; [1] p., dated Oct. 29, 1959 (Box-folder 234/9)
    - Sketch; [1] p., dated Nov. 2, 1959 (Box-folder 234/9)
    - Sketch; [2] p., dated Nov. 6, 1959 (Box-folder 234/9)
    - Printed manuscript piano-vocal scores; 2 p. each, 2 copies (Box-folder 234/9)
    - Typescript lyric sheets; [10] leaves (Box-folder 234/9)
  - It isn't what he said, but the way he said it
    - Manuscript piano-vocal score; [4] p. (Box-folder 234/10)
  - I'm a sucker for a dame see You're a sucker for a dame
  - It takes more than love
    - Typescript lyric sheet; [1] leaf (Box-folder 234/11)
  - Italian song
    - Sketch; [1] p., At top near title: Belle Baker (Box-folder 234/12)
  - It's a walk-in with Walker
    - Piano-vocal score printed on back of newspaper and photocopy; [2] p. each (Box-folder 234/13)
    - Typescript lyric sheets; [5] leaves (Box-folder 234/13)
  - It's about time
    - Typescript lyric sheets; [4] leaves, With annotations (Box-folder 234/14)
    - Typescript lyric sheets; [6] leaves (Box-folder 234/14)
  - It's all in the game, Alternate title: Come on and make me angry
    - Holograph lyric sheet; [1] leaf (Box-folder 234/15)
  - It's the little bit of Irish
    - Manuscript piano-vocal score; 3 p. (Box-folder 234/16)
    - Typescript lyric sheets; [3] leaves (Box-folder 234/16)
  - It's the same in every language, Introduced in Say it with music
    - Sketch; [5] p. (Box-folder 234/17)
    - Typescript lyric sheets; [2] leaves, With annotations (Box-folder 234/17)
    - Typescript lyric sheets; [7] leaves (Box-folder 234/17)
  - It's up to the band, Originally written for Ziegfeld follies of 1927
    - Photocopy of sheet music, Without cover (Box-folder 234/18)
  - I've got a lot of love for you, Alternate title: I love your Ma
    - Manuscript lead sheet; [1] p. (Box-folder 234/19)
    - Typescript lyric sheets; [2] leaves (Box-folder 234/19)
  - I've got a song
    - Sketch; [2] p. (Box-folder 234/20)
  - I've got an ear for music see also If you haven't got an ear for music
    - Sketch; [2] p. (Box-folder 234/21)
    - Typescript lyric sheets; [2] leaves (Box-folder 234/21)
  - I've got my Captain working for me now
    - Fair copy (Kresa) manuscript piano-vocal score; 5 p. (Box-folder 234/22)
    - Typescript lyric sheet; [1] leaf (Box-folder 234/22)
  - I've got to catch a train, goodbye
    - Manuscript lead sheet; [1] p. (Box-folder 234/23)
    - Typescript lyric sheets; [4] leaves (Box-folder 234/23)
  - I've got to have some lovin' now
    - Manuscript piano-vocal score; [3] p. (Box-folder 234/24)
  - I've lost my heart
    - Sketches; [2] p., On verso: sketch with quotation from "La Marseillaise" (Box-folder 234/25)
  - I've written another melody
    - Holograph lyric sheet; [1] leaf (Box-folder 234/26)
  - I've written another song
    - Typescript lyric sheet; [1] leaf (Box-folder 234/26)
  - Jake! Jake! The Yiddish ball player see also Ike, Ike (the Yiddish ball player)
    - Manuscript piano-vocal score; [4] p. (Box-folder 234/27)
    - Sketch; [1] p. (Box-folder 234/27)
  - Jingle belles
    - Manuscript score; 17 p., Laid in: Carbon copy of typescript notes for live show; [1] leaf (Box-folder 31/3)
    - Manuscript parts (Box-folder 31/3)
    - Typescript lyric sheet; [1] leaf, Below title: Opening title for the six Rockettes (Box-folder 234/28)
  - Just a blue serge suit
    - Typescript lyric sheets; [8] leaves (Box-folder 234/29)
    - Sheet music, 2 copies; Without cover (Box-folder 234/29)
  - Just a little while
    - Sketch; [1] p. (Box-folder 234/30)
  - Just for you
    - Typescript lyric sheet; [1] leaf (Box-folder 234/31)
  - Just like the rose
    - Negative photocopy of sheet music, No cover (Box-folder 234/32)
  - Just passing through
    - Typescript lyric sheets; [2] leaves (Box-folder 234/33)
  - Just tunes
    - Sketches; [1] p. (Box-folder 234/34)